### CHAROTAR UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY



Accredited Grade 'A+' by NAAC
CHARUSAT Campus, Off Nadiad- Petlad Highway, Changa-388421
(GUJARAT) INDIA



## Chandubhai S Patel Institute of Technology (CSPIT)

## **Event Report (Alumni Activity)**

| Name of Event                    | : | Ethical AI   |
|----------------------------------|---|--|
| Date & Time of Event             | : | 09/08/2024 (2:00 PM to 4:30 PM)                          |
| Venue / Web-Link for Event       | : | Seminar hall, 2 <sup>nd</sup> floor, CSPIT (A6 building) |
| Event Type (Webinar,             | : | Expert Lecture   |
| Workshop, Mock Interview, etc)   |   |  |
| <b>Event Coordinator</b>         | : | Prof. Spoorthy. V  |
| Resource Person Details (if any) | : | Dr. Darshan Pandya                                       |
| Event for (UG/PG/Ph.D.)          | : | UG   |
| No. of Participants              | : | 68   |

| Sr. | Name of Resource Person | Designation, Organization Name and |
|-----|-------------------------|------------------------------------|
| No. |                         | Contact Details of Resource Person |
| 1   | Dr. Darshan Pandya      | Assistant professor, SBM, NMIMS,   |
|     |                         | Mumbai, Maharashtra                |
|     |                         | Phone No.: 9033911504              |

### **Summary of the Event (Maximum 200 words):**

The event titled "Ethical AI" is organized by Department of AI-ML, CSPIT, Charusat. The key objectives of the event are as follows:

- To understand the core principles of ethical AI, including fairness, accountability, transparency, and privacy.
- Emerging trends in AI and their potential ethical implications.
- To analyze the real-world case studies to understand the practical implications of ethical AI.

The participants were from 3<sup>rd</sup> and 5<sup>th</sup> Semesters of AI-ML department, CSPIT. The expert is an alumnus of Mechanical Engineering Department, CSPIT. A total of 68 students attended the event and gained insights on various terminologies involved in Ethics of AI. The event was concluded with a group activity involving all the students who participated actively in the institute.









| Fina       | ncial Details:                     |                    |
|------------|------------------------------------|--------------------|
| Sr.<br>No. | Details                            | Amount<br>(in Rs.) |
| Inco       | me                                 |                    |
| 1.         |                                    |                    |
| 2.         |                                    |                    |
| 3.         |                                    |                    |
| Exp        | enses                              |                    |
| 1.         | Train ticket (Mumbai to Anand)     | 614.05             |
| 2.         | Train ticket (Ahmedabad to Mumbai) | 1229.05            |
| 3.         | Bus (Charusat to Ahmedabad)        | 200.00             |
| 4.         | Auto (Anand to Charusat)           | 150.00             |
| 5.         | Lecture (2:30 hours)               | 2736.00            |
|            | Total:                             | 5000.00            |

## **Enclosures:-**

- 1. CV/Resume with Photo of Resource Person
- 2. List of Participants
- 3. Event Feedback Summary

| Spoorthity                       | A                    | Balala              |
|----------------------------------|----------------------|---------------------|
| Spoorthy. V<br>Event Coordinator | Secretary, CAA-CSPIT | Chairman, CAA-CSPIT |

### Enclosure-1: CV/Resume with Photo of Resource Person

#### Contact

dhpan96@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/darshanpandya-ph-d-80387424 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Gap Analysis
Problem Solving
Teamwork

#### Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Hindi (Native or Bilingual) Gujarati (Native or Bilingual)

#### Certifications

Al Trends

#### **Publications**

Industry 4.0 Technologies for Sustainable Performance in Indian Manufacturing MSMEs

How Foxconn's Expansion to Vietnam Offers Lessons for Al-Based Solutions for Supply Chain Resilience

Smart, Stylish, and Sustainable: How can Al bring Eco-Friendly Fashion to the Forefront?

Holistic Hospital Operations Management with Industry 4.0 Technologies

Surviving and Thriving in the Face of Political and Economic Disruption: Strategies for Effective Supply Chain Management

## Darshan Pandya, Ph.D.

Assistant Professor, Operations Management and Data Sciences Area, School of Business Management, NMIMS University Mumbai | Ph.D. in Operations Management, Indian Institute of Management Raipur

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

#### Summary

I teach courses on Operations Management, Supply Chain Management, and Business Analytics to MBA students. My research interests include the applications of Industry 4.0 technologies, such as AI and Big Data, to improve sustainability in MSMEs. I have published multiple articles in reputed journals and magazines, such as Journal of Business and Industrial Marketing, Service Business, and IndiaAI, and received a several certification relevant to analytics and AI. I am passionate about using my analytical skills and domain expertise to help businesses and society achieve their sustainability goals.

#### Experience

SVKM's Narsee Monjee Institute of Management Studies (NMIMS) 1 year 8 months

Assistant Professor

March 2024 - Present (6 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

#### Teaching Fellow

January 2023 - April 2024 (1 year 4 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

### Education

Indian Institute of Management Raipur
Doctor of Philosophy - PhD, Operations Management Area · (2018 - 2023)

CHAROTAR UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Mechanical Engineering · (2014 - 2018)

Page 1 of 1

# **Enclosure-2: List of Participants**

| Sr. | Student ID / Emp. |                                   |                            |        |
|-----|-------------------|-----------------------------------|----------------------------|--------|
| No. | ID                | Name of Participant               | Email                      | Mobile |
| 1   | 23AIML038         | DHWANI NAVADIA                    | 23AIML038@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 2   | 23AIML030         | KUKADIYA SANSKRUTI BHARATBHAI     | 23AIML030@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 3   | 23AIML039         | PADMANI RONI ASHVINBHAI           | 23AIML039@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 4   | 23AIML012         | DAVDA YASH ASHOKBHAI              | 23AIML012@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 5   | 23AIML022         | ISOTIYA DHAIRYA MUKESHBHAI        | 23AIML022@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 6   | 23AIML024         | KAKADIYA DEEPKUMAR HARESHBHAI     | 23AIML024@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 7   | 23AIML071         | THUMMAR YUG BHARATBHAI            | 23AIML071@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 8   | 23AIML018         | DOSHI AAGAM NIKHIL                | 23AIML018@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 9   | D23AIML065        | RAVAL AVI RITESHKUMAR             | D23AIML065@charusat.edu.in |        |
| 10  | 23AIML010         | CHOKSI OM CHIRAGBHAI              | 23AIML010@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 11  | 22AIML027         | PANSURIYA NENSIBEN SANJAYBHAI     | 22AIML027@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 12  | 22AIML005         | BHOJANI ISHITABEN RAJESHBHAI      | 22AIML005@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 13  | 22AIML009         | DOBARIYA ZULI JAYSHUKHBHAI        | 22AIML009@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 14  | 22AIML028         | PARMAR KRUSHNAKUMAR DHARMESHBHAI  | 22AIML028@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 15  | 22AIML030         | ARK SANJAYKUMAR PATEL             | 22AIML030@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 16  | 22AIML037         | PATEL NIYATI SHRAMIKKUMAR         | 22AIML037@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 17  | 22AIML036         | MILI BHUPESH PATEL                | 22AIML036@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 18  | 22AIML033         | PATEL HETVI KETANKUMAR            | 22AIML033@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 19  | 22AIML034         | PATEL HETVI NARESHKUMAR           | 22AIML034@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 20  | 22AIML039         | PATEL VIDHI AMITKUMAR             | 22AIML039@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 21  | 22AIML038         | PATEL RISHI JITENDRABHAI          | 22AIML038@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 22  | 22AIML003         | BHANUSHALI HARSH ASHVINBHAI       | 22AIML003@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 23  | D23AIML062        | KOTAK MANYA PRASHANTBHAI          | D23AIML062@charusat.edu.in |        |
| 24  | 22AIML058         | VALA KUNJALBA SANJIVSINH          | 22AIML058@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 25  | 22AIML047         | SHAH MOXIT JINESHBHAI             | 22AIML047@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 26  | 22AIML053         | SONI MALAK DIPAKKUMAR             | 22AIML053@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 27  | 22AIML021         | MEHTA VISHAL SANJAYKUMAR          | 22AIML021@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 28  | 22AIML061         | AHIR HARSH KETANKUMAR             | 22AIML061@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 29  | 22AIML024         | MODI HARSH DHARMENDRAKUMAR        | 22AIML024@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 30  | 22AIML018         | KUNVARIYA UMESHKUMAR SHAILESHBHAI | 22AIML018@charusat.edu.in  |        |
| 31  | 22AIML057         | TRIVEDI MEET PARESHBHAI           | 22AIML057@charusat.edu.in  |        |

| 32 | 22AIML019  | MAHESHWARI HARSH DINESHBHAI    | 22AIML019@charusat.edu.in  |
|----|------------|--------------------------------|----------------------------|
| 33 | 22AIML060  | VYAS PRIYAM ANAND              | 22AIML060@charusat.edu.in  |
| 34 | 22AIML052  | SOLANKI VIVEK DIPAKBHAI        | 22AIML052@charusat.edu.in  |
| 35 | 22AIML055  | THAKKAR MANAV SANJAYBHAI       | 22AIML055@charusat.edu.in  |
| 36 | 22AIML004  | BHANUSHALI JANVI DEEPAK        | 22AIML004@charusat.edu.in  |
| 37 | 22AIML014  | GOSWAMI NIDHIBEN HITESHGIRI    | 22AIML014@charusat.edu.in  |
| 38 | 22AIML043  | SARVAIYA OM MANISHBHAI         | 22AIML043@charusat.edu.in  |
| 39 | D23AIML067 | VIRANI KUNJ NILESHBHAI         | D23AIML067@charusat.edu.in |
| 40 | 22AIML006  | BORDA AKSHATKUMAR MAHESHBHAI   | 22AIML006@charusat.edu.in  |
| 41 | 23AIML006  | BOGHARA ROMIL BHARATBHAI       | 23AIML006@charusat.edu.in  |
| 42 | 22AIML001  | BAMBHROLIYA OM PRAFULBHAI      | 22AIML001@charusat.edu.in  |
| 43 | 22AIML002  | BARAI AUM DHIRENBHAI           | 22AIML002@charusat.edu.in  |
| 44 | 22AIML007  | DEVARSHI DAVE                  | 22AIML007@charusat.edu.in  |
| 45 | 22AIML008  | DESAI KESHA MIRALBHAI          | 22AIML008@charusat.edu.in  |
| 46 | 22AIML022  | JITEN JAYESHKUMAR MISTRY       | 22AIML022@charusat.edu.in  |
| 47 | 22AIML008  | DESAI KESHA MIRALBHAI          | 22AIML008@charusat.edu.in  |
| 48 | 22AIML044  | SATASIYA LIZA HARESHBHAI       | 22AIML044@charusat.edu.in  |
| 49 | 22AIML045  | SAVALIYA ZEEL ANILBHAI         | 22AIML045@charusat.edu.in  |
| 50 | 23AIML025  | KAKADIYA HARSH PANKAJBHAI      | 23AIML025@charusat.edu.in  |
| 51 | 23AIML031  | KUNJADIYA KRISH DILIPKUMAR     | 23AIML031@charusat.edu.in  |
| 52 | 23AIML061  | SAPARA NEMISH CHIMANBHAI       | 23AIML061@charusat.edu.in  |
| 53 | 23AIML045  | PARMAR PUNITSINH JAGDISHSINH   | 23AIML045@charusat.edu.in  |
| 54 | 23AIML016  | DONGA KHUSHIBEN VIJAYBHAI      | 23AIML016@charusat.edu.in  |
| 55 | 23AIML032  | KYADA JULIBEN YOGESHBHAI       | 23AIML032@charusat.edu.in  |
| 56 | 23AIML067  | SHELADIYA MITANG RAJESHBHAI    | 23AIML067@charusat.edu.in  |
| 57 | 23AIML026  | TWISHA DIPAKKUMAR KAMANI       | 23AIML026@charusat.edu.in  |
| 58 | 23AIML068  | SORTHIYA YASHVI NILESHBHAI     | 23AIML068@charusat.edu.in  |
| 59 | 23AIML002  | AHIR JAIMI MUKESHBHAI          | 23AIML002@charusat.edu.in  |
| 60 | 23AIML013  | DEVANI PARTH ASHVINBHAI        | 23AIML013@charusat.edu.in  |
| 61 | 23AIML009  | CHODVADIYA KRISHNA RAJESHKUMAR | 23AIML009@charusat.edu.in  |
| 62 | 23AIML003  | ANSHU BHATT                    | 23AIML003@charusat.edu.in  |
| 63 | 23AIML059  | TITHI PANKAJ RADIA             | 23AIML059@charusat.edu.in  |
| 64 | 23AIML069  | TANK UNNATI PANKAJBHAI         | 23AIML069@charusat.edu.in  |